<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobile Loaner</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_more">More</string>

    <string name="terms">

       <b>Terms &amp; Conditions</b> \n\n\n

By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply
to you - you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully
before using the app. You are not allowed to copy, or modify the app,
any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You are not allowed to
attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also should not try
to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.
The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and
other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Mobile Loaner.\n\n\n\n

Mobile Loaner is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient
as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app
or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never
charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you are paying for.\n\n

The Mobile Loaner app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us,
in order to provide my Service. It is your responsibility to keep your phone and
recommend access to the app secure. We therefore that you do not jailbreak or root
your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations
imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone
vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phones security
features and it could mean that the Mobile Loaner app wont work properly or at all.\n\n

The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions.\n\n

Link to Terms and Conditions of third party service providers used by the app.\n\n

         <b>Google Play Services</b>\n\n

You should be aware that there are certain things that Mobile Loaner will not take responsibility
for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection.
The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Mobile Loaner cannot
take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you do not have access to
Wi-Fi, and you do not have any of your data allowance left.\n\n

If you are using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of
the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged
by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing
the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you are accepting responsibility for any
such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory
(i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the
device on which you are using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission
from the bill payer for using the app.\n\n

Along the same lines, Mobile Loaner cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e.
You need to make sure that your device stays charged - if it runs out of battery and you cannot turn
it on to avail the Service, Mobile Loaner cannot accept responsibility.\n\n

With respect to Mobile Loaners responsibility for your use of the app, when you are using the app,
it is important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct
at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available
to you. Mobile Loaner accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of
relying wholly on this functionality of the app.\n\n


At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently
available on Android - the requirements for system(and for any additional
systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and
you will need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Fast
Loan does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant
to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device.
However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you,
We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time
without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination,\n\n

(a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end\n\n

(b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.\n\n

        <b>Changes to This Terms and Conditions</b>\n\n

I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to
review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by
posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.\n\n

        <b>Contact Us</b>\n\n

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to
contact me at mobileloanerindia@gmail.com.\n\n\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="privacy">

  <b>Privacy policy</b>\n\n\n

Mobile Loaner built the Mobile Loaner app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by
Mobile Loaner at no cost and is intended for use as is.\n\n

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection,
 use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.\n\n

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information
 in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that collect is used for providing
 and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as
 described in this Privacy Policy.\n\n

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions,
which is accessible at Mobile Loaner unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n\n

Information Collection and Use\n\n

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us
 with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to We
 are integrated UPI Payment and If user have face any transaction issue he/she need to
 contact directly admin.If user have complete the process then he/she need to send mail
  to admin for reference. We are taking camera permission for getting image from camera
  and we are not store any data of user externally Mobile Loaner is merely facilitates a transaction
  between two such persons (i.e. Users). Mobile Loaner is not an organization registered with the
  Reserve Bank of India and does not hold any license to engage in any activities relating to
  lending or borrowing. Mobile Loaner is not a Financial institution under the Companies Act, 2013
  or the Banking Regulation Act, 1949 or any other laws for the time being in force in India.
   Mobile Loaner is also not a deposit taking company or a chit fund or a company offering any investment
   schemes as per the rules and regulations for the time being in force in India.\n\n

Mobile Loaner is a service provider facilitating the access between financial institutes and non-banking
finance companies willing to lend and person in need of borrowing. The final decision as regards lending
and borrowing is also subject to the choice of the respective Users in their respective capacities as
lenders / borrowers /users of other financial products as set out in the Platform. Mobile Loaner, through its
Platform displays various products provided by its partners or third parties. In addition to the foregoing,
Mobile Loaner also provides certain other services with respect to data analytics subject to these Terms &amp; Conditions.
 The information that request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.\n\n

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.\n\n

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app\n\n

Google Play Services\n\n

Google Analytics for Firebase\n\n

Firebase Crashlytics\n\n

Log Data\n\n

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data
and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include
information such as your device Internet Protocol (IP) address, device name, operating system version,
the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n\n

<b>Cookies</b>\n\n

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers.
These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your devices internal memory.\n\n

This Service does not use these <b>cookies</b> explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and
libraries that use "cookies" to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to
 either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose
 to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.\n\n

<b>Service Providers</b>\n\n

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\n\n

To facilitate our Service\n\n

To provide the Service on our behalf\n\n

To perform Service-related services or\n\n

To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\n\n

I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information.
The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose
or use the information for any other purpose.\n\n

        <b>Security</b>>\n\n

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable
means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage
is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n

Links to Other Sites\n\n

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
 Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy
 of these websites. have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices
 of any third-party sites or services.\n\n

 Children Privacy\n\n

 These Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information
  from children under 18. In the case I discover that a child under 18 has provided me with personal information,
  I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has
  provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.\n\n

 Changes to This Privacy Policy\n\n

 I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes.
  will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n\n

 This policy is effective as of 2020-07-07\n\n

 <b>Contact Us</b>\n\n

 If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at 
        mobileloanerindia@gmail.com.\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="about_us">
        <b>About this app</b>\n\n\n

Instant personal loan upto 2 lakh for 65 days to 24 month at 0-2.49 per month\n\n

Loans range from 1000 to 200000\n\n

Tenure 65 days to 24 months, interest rates range from 0%-29.95% depending on risk profile of customer and product availed\n\n

Example :if loan amount is 50000 and interest is 22% per annum with tenure of 12 moth and 24 month
 per annum with tenure of 65 days after deducting any other fees\n\n

Mobile Loaner is an interest personal loan app &amp; credit platform for young professional across India,
 where one can apply for personal loan online &amp; avail up to 2 Lakhs as direct cash Transfer to bank account\n\n

<b>Loan Types</b>\n\n

Flexi Personal Loan- A flexible loan option where you can avail loans within 10 minutes of app in…
Online purchase loan -A loan option where you can Buy anything Now,pay later in EMIS.\n\n

<b>Features</b>\n\n

1.100% online process\n\n

2. Minimal documentation\n\n

3. Fast approval\n\n

4. Immediate bank transfer\n\n

        <b>Benefits &amp; Risks</b>\n\n

1. Get access to higher amounts &amp; tenures as you repay on time\n\n

2. As compliance requirement you payment behaviour is shared with credit rating agencies based on that your 
credit score may increase / decrease\n\n

<b>Eligibility</b>\n\n

1. Indian resident\n\n

2. Above the age of 21 years\n\n

3. Should have monthly source of income\n\n

<b>How to get started</b>\n\n

1. Install Mobile Loaner App\n\n

2. Register through your mobile number\n\n

3. Fill your basic details to check forest level eligibility 4. Upload KYC documents -ID,Address Proof &amp; PAN card\n\n

5. Avail loan as bank transfer\n\n

<b>Amount, Tenure, Fees &amp; Charges</b>\n\n

Loans amount :1000 to 200000, Tenure: 65 days to 24 months. Instant loan charges one-time service fee while 
onboarding or during upgrade membership band availed by customer. Interest rates range from 0%-2.49% only. 
A small processing fee is charged for loans e.g for low risk customers 2.5%-6.5% *. The charges and repayment 
tenures vary based on creditworthiness and repayment ability of customer.\n\n

Penalty is charged only when someone delays their scheduled payment.\n\n

The APR for different product is separate as per the risk profile of the customer. The APR for different
 personal loan products: low risk customers is 0% -36%, medium risk customers is 18 % -39% high risk customer 
 is 24% -42%* and very high risk customer is 24%-70%*\n\n

In addition to it,GST will be applicable only on the fee components as per Indian laws.\n\n

*The higher charges are only for loans of lower amount and lower repayment tenure\n\n

Example\n\n

A new low risk customer availing personal loan for salaried can avail a loan of 50,000 at an interest rate of 22% 
processing free of 1,250 for a period of 12 months and onboarding fees of 282. This would translate to APR 25.2%

<b>Interest calculation</b>\n\n

If loan amount is 50,000 &amp; interest 22% per ann and loan is to be repaid over 12 EMIs, then overall interest payable 
is 6,157 only. The EMI per month would be 4,680\n\n

<b>Contact us</b>\n\n

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at 
        mobileloanerindia@gmail.com.\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="loan_rule">If you want to avail loan you need to pay security deposit in order to verify your solvency,
        prepare loan agreement and other services.
        This amount will be adjusted on your repayment</string>


</resources>